THE CHARACTERS, BEHAVIORS, LOCATIONS,
ORGANIZATIONS, PROFESSIONS,
AND VARIOUS INCIDENTS IN THIS SERIES
ARE ENTIRELY FICTIONAL,
CREATED FOR ENTERTAINMENT PURPOSES ONLY,
WITHOUT ANY INTENTION TO REFERENCE
OR ENCOURAGE ANY ACTIONS
THAT MAY OCCUR IN REALITY.
PLEASE USE DISCRETION WHEN VIEWING
Pan!
-Pan!
Where are you, Pan?
Pan!
But if it rains again tonight,
there's a high chance
the existing tracks will be gone.
-Mom.
-Can you search through the night?
Huh?
I'll pay you, I will.
Mom, do you have a tissue?
I'm bleeding.
It's not about money, ma'am.
I just…
I don't know what else to do.
I'm scared I won't get Pan back.
What if she's cold?
Or…
What if someone's hurting her?
What if she's hungry?
Will she wait for me?
If you told me
to burn the whole forest down,
I'd do it. I would.
It's not that serious yet, ma'am.
Look,
I'll go tell the team to search for
an extra hour past shift.
Thank you. Thank you so much, truly.
Not at all, we're all in this together.
Mom.
What.
Hey!
Can't you see I'm out here
looking for Pan?
A scratch like that
and you can't handle it yourself?
-Ow, it hurts, Mom.
-Come here!
Gently, Mom!
Here!
It's nothing!
Pan!
Where are you, Pan?
Hey hey,
stand over there for a sec.
-Here?
-Yeah.
The light is perfect right now.
Give me a smile.
Where'd you learn photography?
My sister taught me.
We were close, my sister and I.
But not close with Mom at all.
You could say…
I'm the daughter my mother never loved.
My sister got to go study in Bangkok.
But I'm stuck in this dead-end district,
I can't go anywhere.
My mom might not even be grieving
because her daughter disappeared.
She might just be grieving
that the wrong daughter is dead.
Your sister isn't dead though,
she just disappeared.
If that's the case…
that's worse than being dead.
Place your hand and touch here.
Come here a sec.
Hey,
there's blood here.
But it's dried.
Could be animal blood.
But there's no body anywhere around here.
Is it possible
Chee was killed right here?
would've left a lot more mess than this.
But maybe Chee wasn't dead yet
at that point
maybe he was still running.
You know, if we actually find the killer,
Chawin's offering 10 million.
10 million.
You want it?
Who wouldn't?
If I had that money
I'd get out of here immediately.
Don't you want it?
wasn't really thinking about that
but if you want it,
I can help.
Are you crazy?
Why wait until you have money
to leave this place?
Well if you don't have money,
where would you even go?
But with that kind of money
you could go anywhere.
10 million, you know.
Split it 50/50?
No,
you take it all.
That's insane.
I'm just bored,
so I want to help.
Playing detective
sounds kind of fun actually.
Do you like it?
Yeah.
Good.
Is Ms. Proud home?
That's me.
May I come in to talk for a moment?
Of course.
Sergeant, wait out here.
Yes.
Come in, come in.
The house is a bit messy,
haven't had guests in years.
Would you like some juice?
I happen to have grape juice.
Oh, that's alright. Just water is fine.
Ah, okay.
MISSING PERSON
This is Pan,.
my eldest daughter.
She takes after you, beautiful.
Oh, not quite.
But she was a good girl. Smart.
Everyone in the community loved her.
Mm. Here you go.
Thank you.
Come sit, come sit.
You see,
I actually wanted to ask you
about Chee, Ms. Proud.
Oh
just call me Auntie,
no need for formalities.
Chee,
hm.
So young, so full of life.
But he really went through a lot.
Like what?
I hate to even bring it up.
Hey..
You know,
Chee's mother
passed away four years ago.
I'm aware.
And do you know how she died?
She hanged herself.
At home.
And from what I heard,
Chee was the one who found the body.
And…
Was Chee close with his father?
Honestly, I'm not sure.
But Mr. Chawin,
his father,
worked incredibly hard.
And back when
Chee and Pan were together,
before Pan disappeared,
those two were absolutely inseparable.
I always figured
Chee
probably saw me as a second mother to him.
So he'd come eat here often.
I'm sorry.
And then after Chee's mother passed,
he became a completely different person.
And then Pan disappeared shortly after
on top of that
Officer, you know how it is with men,
when they're completely shattered,
they change forever.
They can't heal.
It's not like us women.
Either way,
please, look after Chee's case for me.
If you've ever had a child,
you'd understand
how painful it is.
I've been through it myself,
so I can't help but worry.
I know
it's terrible.
I worry so much.
A man left all alone, losing his child,
and with no
wife to look after him either.
It's heartbreaking.
It really is heartbreaking, you know.
It really is.
Lieutenant, are you alright?
If you're here to ask about Jo,
don't bother,
I don't know anything about it at all.
It's just a waste of time.
When was the last time you met him?
A few days ago.
Chee is dead.
Now it's Jo.
Do you understand what this means?
Finding a scapegoat.
It means
there's a psycho bastard
who's hunting all of your gang members.
Even Chee couldn't make it.
I'm just waiting until it's your turn.
Could it be that you have
no chance of dying,
because you're the perpetrator?
To be honest,
it'd be nice
if everyone in your gang dies.
You guys are a waste of space.
Don't stress about it.
things will quiet down soon enough.
I don't know how you guys
handle things here,
or the politics within.
But there are kids dying like this,
one after another.
Aren't we as police
going to do anything at all?
Somethings just couldn't be solved,
that's all.
If you can't solve it,
just let it go.
If you still refuse
to stop talking nonsense
and unethically,
I will seriously report your behavior.
I'm just worried.
A small district like this,
only has government officials
passing through
to take benefits and leave.
People here take care of themselves,
watch their own backs.
As
for the young ones,
they go to big cities for work
and leave a small district
like this to rot.
Only people that are still staying here
are those who gain benefits
from this district.
I think you should know by now
why Inspector Tang still remains here.
Once there are no more benefits,
he'd be the first to leave this town.
You don't have to be so serious about it.
WARIPASOP DISTRICT
PROVINCIAL POLICE STATION
Any progress on the case?
May I speak to you privately?
You guys continue working.
-Yes, sir.
-Alright, this way please.
What is it, Lieutenant?
Why did your wife commit suicide?
I thought you came about my son.
It might be related to the case.
My wife had depression.
Toward the end, she didn't take her meds,
so she committed suicide.
But…
I don't understand
why this is related to Chee's case.
You see, after your wife passed away,
Cheei's temperament
became more aggressive, right?
Yes.
He was the first
to witness his mom's body.
Mom.
Mom. Mom! Mom!
Mom!
Mom.
Mom. Mom!
Someone help!
Hey!
Mom!
He grieved badly.
Then Pan disappear after that.
What are you trying to say?
I'm saying that perhaps
the three cases
are related.
What are you insinuating?
Might as well say it directly.
I'm not insinuating anything.
I'm only asking about the case.
I don't know where
you heard such nonsense from.
But don't ask me
these stupid kinds of questions.
My wife and son are both dead.
Now I have to endure this kind of insult
from a cop like you?
I think you should use your time
to catch the perpetrator instead.
Wait, please calm down
and listen to me first.
No.
If you're going to ask me
things like this again,
don't bother showing up here again.
Chee had never done anything to anyone!
The dead are already dead!
Well,
I don't know what to say.
I'm really sorry, Mr. Chawin.
It won't happen again.
Excuse me.
I already told you about Chawin, right?
I was just doing my job.
I've never stopped you
from doing anything.
But why were you messing with his family?
How is it your business?
Don't let this happen again.
Or else you'll get into trouble.
What are you reading?
Just a normal fashion magazine, Mom.
The kind you never let me read.
Huh?
Why don't I remember that?
You never remember anything, Mom.
Not when you hit Pin or yell at me.
I'm really sorry.
I really didn't know.
It's alright, Mom.
Because
I'm not here anymore.
I'm sorry. I'm really sorry.
I'm sorry.
How should we do it?
Yeah.
Why don't you try sitting?
Is this okay?
Yeah.
Should you lean a little to the side?
Ah-ha.
One. Two.
What are you two doing?
And what is that?
Huh?
Dad's camera?
Who told you to use it?
Mom, I'm just playing around with Pin.
And what are you wearing?
Huh?
What?
Why is it so skimpy?
You brought this
for your big sister to wear?
Pan put it on herself.
I'm just taking photos.
That's not true.
I've never bought
this kind of clothes for her.
Do you think your big sister
is a lowly woman? Huh?
Mom! Pan!
Mom! I'm just taking photos of Pan!
Taking photos?
Why can't you wear normal clothes?
I'm hurt! Pan!
Pan, please tell her!
Wearing it because you want to?
You want to use the camera
and you just use it?
Pan!
Mom, enough! I'm hurt!
Enough! I'm hurt! Pan!
Don't do it next time!
Chee is gone now.
I'll leave everything to you, Que.
SISTER RAY CHILL CHILL STREET FOOD
Cheers! More please. More. Thank you!
Me too!
Let me go take order first.
Come back quickly!
Here's your menu,
what would you like to order?
Spicy minced pork salad and beer.
We ran out of pork,
can you wait for someone to deliver?
Would you like something else first?
There's beef and duck salad.
Beer and nuts then.
Alright. Please wait.
Someone killed Jo.
Here's beer and nuts.
Two members of our gang got killed.
Could it be the same person
who killed Chee?
If we caught them, we can get 10 million!
Damn, I miss Cheei.
Why do you even miss him?
Chee's already dead.
Now,
I can be the one to rule here.
Woo!
Damn, it's so satisfying, you know?
-His dad is powerful but so what?
-Yeah.
Look at my dad, also a soldier!
Yeah! Don't let 'em win!
Did you know?
Chee's woman,
Pan,
I already slept with her!
Hey.
It's Pan's sister.
So what?
Oh hey, Pin.
Your mom allowed you
to drink like others now?
You shut your mouth, M.
Shut my mouth?
Can you shut your mouth
and open something else?
Woo!
Look at her, she's grown up
and just as busty as her sister!
What's wrong with you?
I'm just joking around.
Go play with your mom!
You think you're tough? Huh?
You think you're tough?
Calm down!
Stop!
If you don't stop,
I'll call the police.
None of your business!
Calm down. Easy there.
Don't fight with women.
Let's go drink instead.
Enough, believe me. Let's go drink.
Let's drink.
Stinks of pork!
Easy there.
Sister, two spicy minced pork salad.
More ice, please.
What's wrong?
A wound from chopping pigs up.
Where's your ring?
I don't know either.
I'll get you a change of clothes,
wait a bit.
What are you doing?
Why are you shy? We're both women here.
-Ouch!
-Hold still.
It hurts.
You're not going to die from it.
Your shirt is also dirty.
Why don't you get changed too?
Hey, right here?
Mmm.
I'll wait outside.
Hey!
Pin!
Are you alright?
Nothing's wrong.
I just kicked the edge of the table.
What the?
What the hell is that?
Ouch! Ahh!
Help!